Get ready for the anniversary party. Today is Bhaiya
Bhabhi's anniversary and we are going to the
party, so let's get ready for it.
So guys, today I will tell you about the best foundation.
I have used many brands
of foundation, but after foundation, I get a
lot of pimples on my face.
I went to Tarn Taran from there,
Bhaiya gave me this foundation from Juke Studio,
Oji. My God, what an ultimate
foundation it is, it is very good. You can wear it the whole day, it does not
cake at all. So guys, this is the
foundation which I applied, it was
ultimate for me, by God, so I thought why
not share my experience with you.
This is the highlighter from Smash Box,
lip
liner from Sugar. Makeup is done. Now let's wear jewellery.
All my makeup is done. On top of this, I
wore a long coat.